acteva.com 2007-10-12

# Online event registration for easy event management

|  |  Effective Date: June 1, 2004

Acteva reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users through a notice posted on Acteva.com or by email, of the existence of a new privacy policy or any updates.

**What We Do**  
We at Acteva provide our proprietary online registration, ticketing and payment solution for organizer's events, memberships, donations, licenses and other offerings.

**Information Collection & Use**  
**For Event Organizers**  
Acteva collects personally identifying information only during the registration process. Information is collected in certain portions of Acteva in which clients specifically and knowingly provide such information. Acteva may use such information for its internal purposes, including, but not limited to, editorial and feedback purposes.

Information submitted at the time of registration (including newsletter subscriptions) may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by Acteva and may be shared with companies that have something of value to offer but only with your expressed permission. We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

**For Ticket Purchasers and Consumers**  
When you purchase tickets, passes, or reservations, memberships or make donations through Acteva, we provide the necessary contact information about you to the event, venue, promoter, performer, sponsoring organization, or other involved third party to ensure the successful fulfillment of your activity arrangements. We also use information you provide during the ticketing or purchase process to customize our site to better meet your specific needs, and to make ongoing improvements to the design and function of the Acteva site as a whole.

When you purchase tickets, we send you an e-mail message confirming the online transaction. At the request of the event organizer, we may send e-mail notifications of important information that could affect your use of those tickets, such as schedule changes, updates, or cancellations. For these reasons, we require that our customers have valid e-mail addresses. We may contact you subsequently to facilitate any registration or payment issues that arise.

We do not license, sell, rent or trade any collected personal information, including contact information or specific information about your transactions or other personally identifiable information unless: (1) you request or authorize it; (2) information is provided to help complete a transaction initiated by you; or (3) the disclosure otherwise is lawfully permitted or requested.

Acteva does provide all end user information collected to our clients, the Organizer. Further, Acteva provides use of the Acteva Email Notification System to the Organizer. The Organizer for your event may choose to use your data for marketing purposes, including but not limited to the use of the Acteva Email Notification System. If you receive an email from the Organizer, via the use of Acteva Email Notification System, you may elect to opt out from receiving any future marketing emails sent via Acteva's Email Notification System. The Organizer may continue to use your data for marketing purposes, including emails.

Acteva makes no warranty or representation as to how the Organizer may use or continue to use the data collected through the Acteva website.

**Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes while at the site. Cookies make Web-surfing easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you'll find cookies at most major Web sites. Cookies help make Acteva better, by showing how and when guests use the site. Many content improvements and updates are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. A cookie lets Acteva remember that you've registered, which allows us to speed up your future activities at our sites. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information.

**Removal from our Database**  
Should you ever wish to be removed from our database, simply contact us and we will be happy to fulfill your request. Additionally, should you wish further clarification of this policy, please do not hesitate to email us at [support@acteva.com](mailto:support@acteva.com)

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our company. |  |
